Inauguration 2009 Sermons and Orations Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Submissions, 2008-2009
  - Zion "Goshert's" United Church of Christ (Lebanon, Pennsylvania)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/54)
    - Miracle Boot Camp, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0059_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Marvin Memorial United Methodist Church (Silver Spring, Maryland)
    - Judgement, Vision, and Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/55)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/55)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/55)
    - Judgement, Vision, and Hope, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0060_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Seaside Center for Spiritual Living (Encinitas, California)
    - Walk the Talk: An Inaugural Message to the President, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/56)
    - Walk the Talk: An Inaugural Message to the President, 2009-01-18, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on 2 CDs; afc2009001_0061_sr01-sr02 (Box 11)
    - Walk the Talk: An Inaugural Message to the President, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0061_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Marlow Methodist Church (Summerdale, Alabama)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/57)
    - Photograph postcard of Marlow United Methodist Church (Box-folder 2/57)
    - One of Two, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0062_sr01
  - Westwood Hills Christian Church (Los Angeles, California)
    - Eyes to the Hills, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/58)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 2/58)
    - Eyes to the Hills, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0063_sr01 (Box 11)
  - First Baptist Church (Block Island, Rhode Island)
    - Living the Dream: Can Anything Good Come out of Harbor Church? 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/59)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/59)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Tucson (Tuscon, Arizona)
    - Getting Unstuck (While the Getting's Good!), 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/60)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/60)
  - Beth David Reform Congregation (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania)
    - Be Who You Are, Believe What You Might Be, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/61)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Jacksonville (Jacksonville, Florida)
    - Obama Nation, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/62)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/62)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/62)
    - Obama Nation, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0067_mv01 (Box 8)
  - First United Methodist Church (Portland, Oregon)
    - Dreams, Awakenings, and Inaugurations, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/63)
    - Remembering the Hungry in Our Midst, 2009-01-18, 1 prayer (Box-folder 2/63)
    - Order of Worship, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/63)
    - Ephemera, 2 brochures and 1 business card (Box-folder 2/63)
    - Dreams, Awakenings, and Inaugurations, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0068_sr01 (Box 11)
    - Dreams, Awakenings, and Inaugurations, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0068_sr02
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Asheville (Asheville, North Carolina)
    - Spirit of Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., 2009-01-8, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/64)
  - Henry David Thoreau Unitarian Universalist Congregation (Stafford, Texas)
    - One More Step, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/65)
  - First Baptist Church (Franklin, Indiana)
    - Three Actions for God and Country, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/66)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/66)
    - Three Actions for God and Country, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0071_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Joliet (Joliet, Illinois)
    - The Meaning of Martin Luther King, Jr., 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/67)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/67)
    - The Meaning of Martin Luther King, Jr., 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0072_sr01 (Box 11)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church (Oakland, California)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, 1 digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0073_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 2/68)
    - St. Paul's Episcopal Church Choral Eucharist, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0073_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Hertford United Methodist Church (Hertford, North Carolina)
    - Sermon on Inauguration of Barack Obama, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 2/69)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 2/69)
  - Judson Memorial Church (New York, New York)
    - Dr. King, What would You Say if You were Alive Today?, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/70)
  - Unitarian Universalist Fellowship of Ames (Ames, Iowa)
    - Barack Obama and the Vision of Martin Luther King, Jr., 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/71)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/71)
    - Mary Sawyer, 2009-01-18, 1 photographic print: color, 4 x 6 in.; afc2009001_0076_ph01 (Box-folder 2/71)
    - Barack Obama and the Vision of Martin Luther King, Jr., 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0076_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Community Church of the Pelhams, United Church of Christ (Pelham, New York)
    - Sermon on Barack Obama's Inauguration, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/72)
  - Lee Heights Community Church (Cleveland, Ohio)
    - A New Generation, 2009-01-18, 72 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0078_sr01-sr72 (Box 11)
  - Third Unitarian Church of Chicago (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/74)
    - Letter, 2009-01-30 (Box-folder 2/74)
    - Annual Celebration of Life in Honor of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 2009-01-18, 15 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0079_sr01-sr15 (Box 11)
  - Machar: The Washington Congregation for Secular Humanistic Judaism (Washington, D.C.)
    - One Nation Indivisible: A Call for Allies, 2009-01-18, 1 digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0080_ms01.doc (Box-folder 2/75)
    - One Nation Indivisible: A Call for Allies, 2009-01-18, 1 slide show: digital ppt file and printed copy; afc2009001_0080_ms02.ppt (Box-folder 2/75)
  - Brown-Hutcherson Ministries (Grand Rapids, Michigan)
    - Being Obedient to God, 2009-01-25, 7 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0081_sr01-sr07 (Box 11)
  - Marlow Methodist Church (Summerdale, Alabama)
    - Photograph postcard of Marlow United Methodist Church (Box-folder 2/76)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0082_sr01
  - Community Synagogue (Port Washington, New York)
    - On the Verge of a New Presidency, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/77)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Nashua (Nashua, New Hampshire)
    - Martin and Barack, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/78)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/78)
    - Martin and Barack, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0084_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Little Union Baptist Church (Shreveport, Louisiana)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/79)
    - One For the Books, 2009-01-18, 8 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0085_sr01-sr08 (Box 11)
  - Islamic Center of Pittsburgh (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania)
    - Friday Sermon of the Islamic Center of Pittsburgh, 2009-01-23, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0086_ms01.doc (Box-folder 2/80)
  - Lutheran Church of the Master (Los Angeles, California)
    - Vision and Dreams, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0087_ms01.doc (Box-folder 2/81)
  - Congregation B'nai Israel (Boca Raton, Florida)
    - An Open Letter to the New President, 2009-01-23, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/82)
  - Iglesia Cristiana Hispana, Discipulos de Cristo (Anniston, Alabama)
    - Tema: El puente hacia el Sueno, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/83)
    - El puente del Sueno, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: CD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0089_sr01 (Box 17)
  - Starr King Unitarian Universalist Church (Hayward, California)
    - King, Obama & Patriotism, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/84)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/84)
    - Photograph of service, 2009-01-18, 1 photographic print: color, 5 x 7 in.; afc2009001_0090_ph01 (Box-folder 2/84)
    - King, Obama & Patriotism, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0090_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Creative Arts Center for Spiritual Living (Los Angeles, California)
    - Practicing the Presence, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0091_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Unity Presbyterian Church (Denver, North Carolina)
    - Never Say Never, 2009-01-04, 1 sermon (Box-folder 2/85)
    - Program, 2009-01-04 (Box-folder 2/86)
    - Never Say Never, 2009-01-04, 1 video recording: DVD [missing]; afc2009001_0092_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Emanuel Lutheran Church (West Warwick, Connecticut)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/86)
  - Lutheran Church of the Newtons (Newton, Massachusetts)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 2/87)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0094_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Stewart Memorial Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Indianapolis, Indiana)
    - God's Plan for Embarking on a New Journey, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0095_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 3/88)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/88)
  - First Unitarian Church of Oklahoma City (Oklahoma City, Oklahoma)
    - Racial Justice: Accomplishments and Aspirations, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0096_ms01.doc (Box-folder 3/89)
  - Heart for the World Christian Center (Aurora, Colorado)
    - The Check Has Been Cashed, 2009-01-25, 7 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0097_sr01-sr07 (Box 11)
  - Providence Missionary Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/90)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/90)
    - Letter, 2009-01-27 (Box-folder 3/90)
    - Mountain Moving Faith for 2009, 2009-01-25, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0098_sr01-sr03 (Box 11)
    - Yes God Can and Did! 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0098_sr04 (Box 11)
  - St. Paul's On-the-Hill Episcopal Church (Saint Paul, Minnesota)
    - Commemoration of Rev. Dr. Martin Luther King, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/91)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/91)
  - Positive Living Center (Oakhurst, California)
    - The Bible and the Bullet, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/92)
  - Mason United Methodist Church (Tacoma, Washington)
    - A Dream Never Dies, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/93)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/93)
    - Letter, 2009-01-21 (Box-folder 3/93)
    - "Library of Congress asks for inauguration sermons," The News Tribune (Tacoma, Washington), 1 news article (Box-folder 3/93)
  - West Hunter Street Baptist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/94)
    - Program, 2008-12-07 (Box-folder 3/94)
    - DVD cover, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/94)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0102_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Mount Tipton Christian Methodist Episcopal Church (Brighton, Tennessee)
    - Inaugural Sermon: Change Has Come to America, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/95)
    - Program, 2009-01-25, 2 copies (1 with signatures) (Box-folder 3/95)
  - Memorial Church Harvard University (Cambridge, Massachusetts)
    - What Dare We Hope For, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon with biographical sketch of Reverend Peter John Gomes (Box-folder 3/96)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/96)
    - Letter, 2009-01-23 (Box-folder 3/96)
  - Ahavath Achim Synagogue (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Sermon Parshat Shemot, 2009-01-17, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/97)
  - Christ Lutheran Church (Dallas, Texas)
    - Live to See the Day, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/98)
  - Victory for the World Church (Stone Mountain, Georgia)
    - I Want to be Blessed Like Barack, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0107_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Faith Presbyterian Church Reformed (Mesquite, Texas)
    - The Favor of the Lord, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: CD [missing]; afc2009001_0108_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Concerned Black Clergy of Metropolitan Atlanta, Inc. (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - State of Community Address, 2009-01-25, 1 speech (Box-folder 3/100)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/100)
    - Invitation to State of the Community Address, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/100)
    - State of Community Address, 2009-01-25, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0109_sr01-sr02 (Box 11)
  - Jean M. Zlotkin (San Francisco, California)
    - E Pluribus Unum (Commemorating Inauguration Day 2009), 2009-01-18, 1 poem (Box-folder 3/101)
  - Washington Ethical Society (Washington, D.C.)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/102)
    - On the Edge of History: Martin Luther King, Jr. Celebration, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0111_sr01 (Box 11)
  - St. Mark's Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - It's Hard to Believe, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (2 copies) (Box-folder 3/103)
    - It's Hard to Believe, 2009-01-18, 2 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0112_sr01-sr02 (Box 11)
    - It's Hard to Believe, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0112_mv01 (Box 8)
    - It's Hard to Believe, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: MiniDV; afc2009001_0112_mv01
  - Coptic Orthodox Diocese of the Southern U.S.
    - Exalted Equality: One Nation Under God, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon: digital pdf file and printed copy; afc2009001_0113_ms01.pdf (Box-folder 3/104)
  - Mount Helm Baptist Church (Jackson, Mississippi)
    - Dreams That Benefit People, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/105)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/105)
    - Photos of the congregation and exterior of the church, 2009-01-18, 12 photographic prints: color, 4 x 6 in.; afc2009001_0114_ph01-ph12 (Box-folder 3/105)
    - Dreams That Benefit People, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0114_sr01
    - Dreams That Benefit People, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0114_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Kent (Kent, Ohio)
    - A Sermonic Letter to My Church to Commemorate Martin Luther King Jr. Sunday, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/106)
  - St. Mark United Methodist Church (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - Stepping Out into the Unknown, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/107)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/107)
    - Photograph of service, 2009-01-25, 1 photograph: color, digital image printout; afc2009001_0116_ph01 (Box-folder 3/107)
    - Stepping Out into the Unknown, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0116_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Lake View Terrace American Baptist Church (Lakeview Terrace, California)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/108)
    - A God, A Hope, A Plan and A Community Organizer, 2009-01-25, 5 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0117_sr01-sr05 (Box 11)
  - St. Augustine's Episcopal Church (Kingston, Rhode Island)
    - Annual Meeting; Epi3B, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/109)
  - Come As You Are Community Church (Fort Wayne, Indiana)
    - God Has a Fixed Time, 2009-01-25, 2 video recordings: digital files submitted on 2 DVDs; afc2009001_0119_mv01-mv02 (Box 8)
  - Congregation Beth Israel (Portland, Oregon)
    - God Revealed- In the Courage to Lead, 2009-01-23, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0120_sr01 (Box 11)
  - St. Mark's United Church of Christ (Baltimore, Maryland)
    - The Trash from Nazareth, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/110)
    - The Hard Call, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/110)
  - Unitarian Universalist Church of Loudon (Leesburg, Virginia)
    - Something Worth Standing For, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0122_ms01.doc (Box-folder 3/111)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, afc2009001_0122_ms02 (Box-folder 3/111)
    - Something Worth Standing For, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0122_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Zwingli United Church of Christ (Belleville, Wisconsin) and Salem United Church of Christ (Campbellsport, Wisconsin)
    - Discipleship: A Miracle of God's Doing, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/112)
    - Program (Zwingli United Church of Christ), 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/112)
    - Covenantal Partners, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/112)
    - Program (Salem United Church of Christ), 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/112)
    - Photographs of church interior, exterior and congregation, 2009-01-25, 5 photographic prints: color, 5 x 8 in. 1 photographic print: color, 9 x 11 in.; afc2009001_0123_ph01-ph06 (Box-folder 3/112)
  - Bethel African Methodist Episcopal Church (Dallas, Texas)
    - Speeches by Rene Davis, Sonya Rundles, and Giana Williams, 2009-01-25, 3 speeches (Box-folder 3/113)
    - Can't You Feel It, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/113)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/113)
    - Photographs of service, 2009-01-25, 5 photographs: color, digital image printouts; afc2009001_0124_ph01-ph05 (Box-folder 3/113)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-25, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0124_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Les Tres Santos Reyes (Baltimore, Maryland)
    - Second Sunday after the Epiphany, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/114)
  - Wellesley Hills Congregational Church (Wellesley, Massachusetts)
    - Church service, 2009-01-18, 5 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0126_sr01-sr05 (Box 11)
  - St. Alban's Episcopal Church (Annandale, Virginia)
    - Second Sunday after the Epiphany, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/115)
  - The 360 Second Word (Atlanta, Georgia)
    - He Did His Part Now We Must Do Ours, 2009-01-26, 1 sound recording: mp3; afc2009001_0128_sr01.mp3
  - Colonial Hills Community of Christ (Blue Springs, Missouri)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/116)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0129_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Arlington Church of the Brethren (Arlington, Virginia)
    - Calling for Change, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0130_ms01.doc (Box-folder 3/117)
    - Program, 2009-01-18, 2 copies (Box-folder 3/117)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: audio cassette tape; afc2009001_0130_sr01
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0130_mv01 (Box 17)
  - Dennis Union Church (Dennis, Massachusetts)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/118)
    - Sermon, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0131_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Community Renewal Society (Chicago, Illinois)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 3/119)
    - Out of the Gloomy Past, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0132_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Westside Unitarian Universalist Church (Seattle, Washington) and East Shore Unitarian Church (Bellingham, Washington)
    - Deepening the Dream: Spiritual Reflections on Being American, 2009-01-18, 12 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0133_sr01-sr12 (Box 11)
  - Antioch Missionary Baptist Church (San Antonio, Texas)
    - Yes We Can, 2009-01-25, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0134_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - What Then Is to Be Done? By Rev. Brian E. Hamilton, 2009-01-11, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/120)
    - Program, 2009-01-11 (Box-folder 3/120)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/121)
    - Sermon by Rev. Ruth W. Hamilton, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital mp3 file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0136_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Unity Church of Harrisburg (Enola, Pennsylvania)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0137_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Temple Sinai (Sumter, South Carolina)
    - The Election of Barack Hussein Obama, 2009-01-16, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/122)
  - Galilee Baptist Church (Suitland, Maryland)
    - When You Are Not in the Line Up, 2009-01-11, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/123)
    - Photo of Rev. Dr. Lloyd T. McGriff, 2009-01-11, 1 photograph: color, digital image printout; afc2009001_0139_ph01 (Box-folder 3/123)
    - When You Are Not in the Line Up, 2009-01-11, 8 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0139_sr01-sr08 (Box 11)
  - Mount Hope Baptist Church (Prince George, Virginia)
    - On the Historic Occasion of the 44th Inaugural Celebration of US President Barack Hussein Obama: It's Simply Marvelous, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0140_ms01.doc (Box-folder 3/124)
    - Photograph of Rev. A. Carl Prince, 2009-01-25, 2 photographs: color, digital, jpg files and printed copies; afc2009001_0140_ph01-ph02.jpg (Box-folder 3/124)
  - Nineteenth Street Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - Sermon, Attended by President Elect Barack Obama and family, 2009-01-18, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0141_sr01-sr03 (Box 11)
  - Congregational Church in Deerfield (Deerfield, Illinois)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/125)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 3/125)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: DVD [faulty disc]; afc2009001_0142_mv01 (Box 11)
  - Yale University Divinity School (New Haven, Connecticut)
    - The Winds of Change, 2009-01-22, 1 sermon (Box-folder 3/126)
    - Program with hymns, 2009-01-22 (Box-folder 3/126)
  - Union Baptist Church (Easton, Maryland)
    - Almost, But Not Yet, 2009-01-18, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0144_ms01.doc (Box-folder 4/127)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/127)
    - The Valley Calls, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon: digital doc file and printed copy; afc2009001_0144_ms03.doc (Box-folder 4/127)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/127)
    - Photographs of Reverend Fentress A. Hickman and church, 2009-01-25, 3 photographs: digital doc files and printed copies; afc2009001_0144_ph01-ph03.doc
  - Rock Springs United Methodist Church (Lawrenceville, Georgia)
    - The Surprising Grace of God, 2009-01-25, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/128)
    - Program, 2009-01-25 (Box-folder 4/128)
  - College Street Congregational Church (Burlington, Vermont)
    - A Litany for Martin Luther, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/129)
    - Program, 2009-01-18 (Box-folder 4/129)
    - Photographs of Reverend David Wright and congregation, 2009-01-18, 5 photographs: color, digital jpg files and printed copies; afc2009001_0146_ph01-ph05.jpg (Box-folder 4/129)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav file submitted on CD; afc2009001_0146_sr01 (Box 11)
  - Progressive Baptist Church (New Orleans, Louisiana)
    - Don't Forget How You Got There, 2009-01-18, 3 sound recordings: digital wav files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0147_sr01-sr03 (Box 11)
  - The Parish Church of Christ the King (Portage, Michigan)
    - Sermon, 2009-01-18, 1 video recording: digital file submitted on DVD; afc2009001_0148_mv01 (Box 8)
  - Positive Living Center (Oakhurst, California)
    - Inauguration, 2009-01-25, 1 poem (Box-folder 4/130)
  - East Friendship Baptist Church (Washington, D.C.)
    - I Wish I Had Time, 2009-01-18, 1 sound recording: digital wav and wma files submitted on CD; afc2009001_0150_sr01 (Box 11)
  - La Canada Congregational Church (La Canada, California)
    - Say it Again, Sam! 2009-01-18, 1 sermon (Box-folder 4/131)